
IdentifyNumber.numberData = [
	{
		"language": "English-Uganda",		//0
		'languageFont':'fonts/Andika-Regular.ttf',
		"gameArray": [
			/* {  
				"gameName": "N39A",
				"queImg": "N39A_2",
				"numberArray": [7, 3, 6, 9],
				"corectAns": 6,            ///////
				"questionText": "<span style='color:blue'>(Point to the picture and say)</span> Look at this carefully. Now place your finger and tell me which of these <span style='color:blue'>(Point to the options)</span> is equal to the number of balls here <span style='color:blue'>(Point to the picture)</span>?",
			}, */
			{  
				"gameName": "N39B",
				"queImg": "N39B_1",
				"numberArray": [6, 8, 9, 5],
				"corectAns": 8,
				"questionText": "Place your finger and show me, which of these <span style='color:blue'>(point to the options)</span> is <b>equals to</b> the number of ducks <b>here</b> <span style='color:blue'>(point to the picture)</span>?",
			},
		]
	},	
	{
		"language": "Hindi-India",			//1
		'languageFont':'',
		"gameArray": [
			/* {  
				"gameName": "N39A",
				"queImg": "N39A_2",
				"numberArray": [7, 3, 6, 9],
				"corectAns": 6,            ///////
				"questionText": "<span style='color:blue'>(Point to the picture and say)</span> Look at this carefully. Now place your finger and tell me which of these <span style='color:blue'>(Point to the options)</span> is equal to the number of balls here <span style='color:blue'>(Point to the picture)</span>?",
			}, */
			{  
				"gameName": "N39B",
				"queImg": "N39B_1",
				"numberArray": [6, 8, 9, 5],
				"corectAns": 8,
				"questionText": "अपनी ऊँगली रखकर मुझे दिखाओ, इनमे से कौनसा <span style='color:blue'>(विकल्पों की ओर इशारा करें)</span> <b>यहाँ</b> <span style='color:blue'>(चित्र की ओर इशारा करें)</span> हंसों की संख्या <b>के बराबर</b> है?",
			},
		]
	},
	{
		"language": "Spanish-Mexico",		//2
		'languageFont':'',
		"gameArray": [
			/* {  
				"gameName": "N39A",
				"queImg": "N39A_2",
				"numberArray": [7, 3, 6, 9],
				"corectAns": 6,            ///////
				"questionText": "",
			}, */
			{  
				"gameName": "N39B",
				"queImg": "N39B_1",
				"numberArray": [6, 8, 9, 5],
				"corectAns": 8,
				"questionText": "Con tu dedo muéstrame, ¿cuál de estos <span style='color:blue'>(señala las opciones)</span> <b>es igual al</b> número de patos <b>aquí</b> <span style='color:blue'>(señala la imagen)</span>?",
			},
		]
	},	
	{
		"language": "Spanish-Nicaragua",	//3
		'languageFont':'fonts/AntarcticaRegular.ttf',
		"gameArray": [
			/* {  
				"gameName": "N39A",
				"queImg": "N39A_2",
				"numberArray": [7, 3, 6, 9],
				"corectAns": 6,            ///////
				"questionText": "",
			}, */
			{  
				"gameName": "N39B",
				"queImg": "N39B_1",
				"numberArray": [6, 8, 9, 5],
				"corectAns": 8,
				"questionText": "Indicá con tu dedo, ¿cuál de estos números <span style='color:blue'>(señale las opciones)</span> es <b>igual</b> a la cantidad de patos aquí en la imagen <span style='color:blue'>(señale la imagen)</span>?",
			},
		]
	},
	{
		"language": "Kiswahili-Kenya",		//4
		'languageFont':'fonts/Andika-Regular.ttf',
		"gameArray": [
			/* {  
				"gameName": "N39A",
				"queImg": "N39A_2",
				"numberArray": [7, 3, 6, 9],
				"corectAns": 6,            ///////
				"questionText": "<span style='color:blue'>(تصویر کی طرف اشارہ کریں اور کہیں)</span> اسے غور سے دیکھو اور انگلی رکھ کر مجھے بتاؤ ان میں سے کونسا عدد <span style='color:blue'>(آپشنز کی طروف اشارہ کریں)</span> یہاں موجود گیندوں کی تعداد <span style='color:blue'>(تصویر کی طرف اشارہ کریں)</span> کے برابر ہے؟",
			}, */
			{  
				"gameName": "N39B",
				"queImg": "N39B_1",
				"numberArray": [6, 8, 9, 5],
				"corectAns": 8,
				"questionText": "Weka kidole chako na unionyeshe, ni ipi kati ya hizi <span style='color:blue'>(onyesha chaguo)</span> ni <b>sawa na</b> idadi ya bata <b>hapa</b> <span style='color:blue'>(onyesha picha)</span>?",
			},
		]
	},
	{
		"language": "French-Senegal",		//5
		'languageFont':'',
		"gameArray": [
			/* {  
				"gameName": "N39A",
				"queImg": "N39A_2",
				"numberArray": [7, 3, 6, 9],
				"corectAns": 6,            ///////
				"questionText": " <span style='color:blue'>(Elekeza kidole kwenye picha kisha useme)</span> Tazama hapa kwa makini. Sasa nionyeshe kwa kidole, ni gani kati ya hizi <span style='color:blue'>(onyesha viteuliwa kwa kidole)</span> ni sawa na idadi ya mipira hapa <span style='color:blue'>(onyesha kwa kidole picha inayorejelewa )</span>.",
			}, */
			{  
				"gameName": "N39B",
				"queImg": "N39B_1",
				"numberArray": [6, 8, 9, 5],
				"corectAns": 8,
				"questionText": "Place ton doigt et montre-moi, lequel de ces <span style='color:blue'>(pointe les options)</span> est <b>égal</b> au nombre de canards <b>ici</b> <span style='color:blue'>(pointe l'image)</span> ? ",
			},
		]
	},
	{
		"language": "Bangla-Bangladesh",	//6
		'languageFont':'fonts/kalpurush.ttf',
		"gameArray": [
			/* {  
				"gameName": "N39A",
				"queImg": "N39A_2",
				"numberArray": [7, 3, 6, 9],
				"corectAns": 6,            ///////
				"questionText": " <span style='color:blue'>(Elekeza kidole kwenye picha kisha useme)</span> Tazama hapa kwa makini. Sasa nionyeshe kwa kidole, ni gani kati ya hizi <span style='color:blue'>(onyesha viteuliwa kwa kidole)</span> ni sawa na idadi ya mipira hapa <span style='color:blue'>(onyesha kwa kidole picha inayorejelewa )</span>.",
			}, */
			{  
				"gameName": "N39B",
				"queImg": "N39B_1",
				"numberArray": ['৬', '৮', '৯', '৫'],
				"corectAns": '৮',
				"questionText": " <span style='color:blue'>(ছবিটি দেখিয়ে বলুন)</span> মনোযোগ দিয়ে পাখিগুলো গুনে দেখো। এখন, তোমার আঙুল দিয়ে দেখিয়ে আমাকে বল তো এগুলোর মধ্যে <span style='color:blue'>(অপশনগুলো দেখান)</span> কোনটি পাখিগুলোর সংখ্যার <span style='color:blue'>(ছবিটি দেখান)</span> সমান?",
			},
		]
	},
	{
		"language": "Nepali-Nepal",			//7
		'languageFont':'fonts/MANGAL.ttf',
		"gameArray": [
			/* {  
				"gameName": "N39A",
				"queImg": "N39A_2",
				"numberArray": [7, 3, 6, 9],
				"corectAns": 6,            ///////
				"questionText": " <span style='color:blue'>(Elekeza kidole kwenye picha kisha useme)</span> Tazama hapa kwa makini. Sasa nionyeshe kwa kidole, ni gani kati ya hizi <span style='color:blue'>(onyesha viteuliwa kwa kidole)</span> ni sawa na idadi ya mipira hapa <span style='color:blue'>(onyesha kwa kidole picha inayorejelewa )</span>.",
			}, */
			{  
				"gameName": "N39B",
				"queImg": "N39B_1",
				"numberArray": [ '९', '५', '८', '६'],
				"corectAns": '८',
				"questionText": "यिनीहरु मध्ये कुन <span style='color:blue'>(विकल्पहरुमा देखाउनुहोस्)</span> <b>यहाँ</b> हाँसको संख्यासँग <b>बराबर</b> हुन्छ आफ्नो औँलाले थिचेर मलाई देखाउनुहोस् <span style='color:blue'>(चित्रलाई देखाउनुहोस्)</span> ।",
			},
		]
	},
	{
		"language": "French-Mali",			//8
		'languageFont':'',
		"gameArray": [
			/* {  
				"gameName": "N39A",
				"queImg": "N39A_2",
				"numberArray": [7, 3, 6, 9],
				"corectAns": 6,            ///////
				"questionText": "<span style='color:blue'>(تصویر کی طرف اشارہ کریں اور کہیں)</span> اسے غور سے دیکھو اور انگلی رکھ کر مجھے بتاؤ ان میں سے کونسا عدد <span style='color:blue'>(آپشنز کی طروف اشارہ کریں)</span> یہاں موجود گیندوں کی تعداد <span style='color:blue'>(تصویر کی طرف اشارہ کریں)</span> کے برابر ہے؟",
			}, */
			{  
				"gameName": "N39B",
				"queImg": "N39B_1",
				"numberArray": [6, 8, 9, 5],
				"corectAns": 8,
				"questionText": "Mets ton doigt sur et montre-moi, lequel de ces <span style='color:blue'>(pointe sur les options)</span> est égal au nombre de canards <b>ici</b> <span style='color:blue'>(pointe sur l’image)</span>?",
			},
		]
	},
	{
		"language": "Kiswahili-Tanzania",	//9
		'languageFont':'',
		"gameArray": [
			/* {  
				"gameName": "N39A",
				"queImg": "N39A_2",
				"numberArray": [7, 3, 6, 9],
				"corectAns": 6,            ///////
				"questionText": "<span style='color:blue'>(تصویر کی طرف اشارہ کریں اور کہیں)</span> اسے غور سے دیکھو اور انگلی رکھ کر مجھے بتاؤ ان میں سے کونسا عدد <span style='color:blue'>(آپشنز کی طروف اشارہ کریں)</span> یہاں موجود گیندوں کی تعداد <span style='color:blue'>(تصویر کی طرف اشارہ کریں)</span> کے برابر ہے؟",
			}, */
			{  
				"gameName": "N39B",
				"queImg": "N39B_1",
				"numberArray": [6, 8, 9, 5],
				"corectAns": 8,
				"questionText": "onyesha kwenye skrini, ipi kati ya hizi <span style='color:blue'>(onesha machaguo)</span> ni <b>sawasawa</b> na idadi ya bata <b>hapa</b> <span style='color:blue'>(onesha picha)</span>?",
			},
		]
	},
	{
		"language": "Urdu-Pakistan",	//10
		'languageFont':'',
		"gameArray": [
			/* {  
				"gameName": "N39A",
				"queImg": "N39A_2",
				"numberArray": [7, 3, 6, 9],
				"corectAns": 6,            ///////
				"questionText": "<span style='color:blue'>(تصویر کی طرف اشارہ کریں اور کہیں)</span> اسے غور سے دیکھو اور انگلی رکھ کر مجھے بتاؤ ان میں سے کونسا عدد <span style='color:blue'>(آپشنز کی طروف اشارہ کریں)</span> یہاں موجود گیندوں کی تعداد <span style='color:blue'>(تصویر کی طرف اشارہ کریں)</span> کے برابر ہے؟",
			}, */
			{  
				"gameName": "N39B",
				"queImg": "N39B_1",
				"numberArray": [6, 8, 9, 5],
				"corectAns": 8,
				"questionText": "اپنی انگلی رکھیں اور مجھے دکھائیں، ان میں سے کون سا نمبر <span style='color:blue'>(آپشنز کی طرف اشارہ کریں)</span> <b>یہاں</b> <span style='color:blue'>(تصویر کی طرف اشارہ کریں)</span> بطخوں کی تعداد کے برابر ہے ؟",
			},
		]
	},
	{
		"language": "Portuguese-Mozambique",	//11
		'languageFont':'',
		"gameArray": [
			/* {  
				"gameName": "N39A",
				"queImg": "N39A_2",
				"numberArray": [7, 3, 6, 9],
				"corectAns": 6,            ///////
				"questionText": "<span style='color:blue'>(تصویر کی طرف اشارہ کریں اور کہیں)</span> اسے غور سے دیکھو اور انگلی رکھ کر مجھے بتاؤ ان میں سے کونسا عدد <span style='color:blue'>(آپشنز کی طروف اشارہ کریں)</span> یہاں موجود گیندوں کی تعداد <span style='color:blue'>(تصویر کی طرف اشارہ کریں)</span> کے برابر ہے؟",
			}, */
			{  
				"gameName": "N39B",
				"queImg": "N39B_1",
				"numberArray": [6, 8, 9, 5],
				"corectAns": 8,
				"questionText": "Coloca o teu dedo aqui e mostra-me, qual desses <span style='color:blue'>(aponte para as opções)</span> é <b>igual a</b> o número de patos <b>aqui</b> <span style='color:blue'>(aponte para a imagem)</span>?",
			},
		]
	},	
];

